<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Your awesome title</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>http://yourdomain.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://yourdomain.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2015 03:05:35 -0300</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2015 03:05:35 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Last of Us</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I have never found these types of playlists to be remotely satisfactory, whether they were created by man or machine. But I was shocked by my experience with the first playlist that Discover Weekly generated for me this week.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2015 20:09:53 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/journal/the-last-of-us</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/journal/the-last-of-us</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Type.js</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A new project from Nathan Ford that uses non-standard CSS rules to provide finer typographic control of web pages, including control over kerning pairs, widows, rags and font-size when using viewport units.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2015 19:55:16 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/journal/type-js</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/journal/type-js</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Martian</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The first review of Andy Weir’s The Martian I read was Jez Burrows’ earlier this year. Despite his misgivings concerning the protagonist’s tone, I couldn’t resist the setup and read it the following week. It’s an engrossing, exhaustively researched tale of resourcefulness whose genesis as a self-published serial is well documented. I’m pretty sure you’ve already read it.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2015 19:43:14 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/journal/the-martian</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/journal/the-martian</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Iceland Bouldering</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This is our organic denim. It’s a beautiful unwashed 12oz denim from a great mill in Turkey. Hard wearing too. Just so you know we are in organic denim forever. But preferably longer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2015 12:50:34 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/journal/iceland-bouldering</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/journal/iceland-bouldering</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
